https://hargrave.edu/privacy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
What the Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Hargrave treats personal information we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of Hargrave products, services, and websites. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone numbers, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Hargrave does not own or control, or to people that Hargrave does not employ or manage, such as partners.
The Information Collected
Hargrave collects personally identifiable information only upon user consent. The information is normally gathered through our forms, newsletters, or other services we offer to users. Information collected may include, but are not exclusive to names, addresses, email addresses, and phone numbers of users of the Hargrave website.
Anonymous information is collected in the form of site and page traffic performance which include geographic and demographic information.
How Private Information Is Protected, Changed, and Updated
All personal information is stored on secure servers only accessible by Hargrave employees.
Account information and deletion of personal identifiable information will be executed upon user request. Any request for deletion will take up to 30 calendar days upon verification.
If you have any questions, please feel free to get in touch with us.
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Parents, cadets, alumni, friends, and all interested in Hargrave are welcome to subscribe.
Stay up to Date
Scroll to Top
